

# 0812 9125 4913 muh.miftah.firdaus@gmail.com

Live at Srengseng Sawah, Jagakarsa, South Jakarta

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Laravel
Codeigniter
MySQL
Javascript
Jquery
Vue JS
Git
UNIX CLI

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Diligent
Discipline
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

## LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia Passive English

# MUHAMMAD MIFTAH FIRDAUS

# WEB DEVELOPER

### **ABOUT**

I have 3 years experience in web developer, especially familiar with Laravel, Codeigniter, Jquery, Javascript, Git, Vue JS, MySQL and have many portfolios. I wanna collaborate, contribute and apply my knowledge & skills for continuous improvement to your company.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **FREELANCE**

Web Developer | Oct 2017 - Now

- Develop and Maintain Asset Management System
- Develop and Maintain Sparring Sport System, https://ayo.co.id
- Develop and Maintain Dashboard Startup Online Shop

### PT. PRAWATHIYA KARSA PRADIPTHA

Web Developer | Apr 2016 - Oct 2017

 Maintain and Enhancement Beyond Technology for Call Center

DIVISION DATA & IT BPSDM MINISTRY OF PUBLIC WORK & HOUSING INDONESIA

IT Staff | Aug 2015 - Mar 2016

- Troubleshoot IT Problem
- Monitoring Data DIKLAT

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SYSTEM COMPUTER
University of Gunadarma | 2010 - 2014
GPA 3.11